Momoko, if you wanna go out with mom,
put away your melodica
I'm sorry
- I'll be back soon.
- OK.
Look at this letter
It's time you replied
You're right
We're leaving
- Momoko, let's go
- Alright
- Goodbye
Take care
Tota
I'm sorry
Manager Tota
She's a new staff member
It's my first day in the Marketing Department
My name is Saya Amami
Nice to meet you
These are our 3 presently undergoing projects
- Familiarize yourself with them
- Yes, madam
- "I be your mentor for the time being
- QK.
Nice to meet you, I'm Kosaka
Nice to meet you
Be careful. Love affair may affect your work
That's nonsense
You'd stay away from Amami
Love affair is a taboo in office,
- especially for women
- Yes
Actually, I'm a cautious person
- Please get this done by tomorrow
- Yes, sir
- Are you getting married?
I heard about it recently
Sorry, I wanted to inform you when the day is set
When is your big day?
In September
You're aggressive in your marriage too
I'm quite cautious in a sense
Excuse me
Manager Tota... how are you?
How are you?
Which one do you recommend?
Anyone will do
I'll choose this one then
Can I sit next to you?
Can I try a mouthful of yours?
I'd have chosen lemon tea as well
They're holding a welcome party
Are you coming too? I really hope you would
I have to work over-time. I'll see if I can make it
Really? What a pity
I'm returning to the office
You shouldn't be late too
Tota
Thanks for your hospitality
Thank you
We're going to the same way. Let me see you home
Your intention is obvious
But I think you're timid
Beware of him
Nonsense, I don't intend to do that
You're so noisy. You're drunk
He's drunk
You
Are you alright?
I'm sorry. I think I'm drunk
I thought I'd hold the liquor
I wonder if manager is still working
Manager doesn't like to hang around with
young people. He's gone home
He's a family man
But he paid his share for the welcome party
He's a good superior
I wish I'd be like him one day
Be successful in career and family
What're you doing?
Look, this picture is nice
Where did we take it?
You forgot? When we were in the amusement park
Yeah
Is this photo frame cute?
I bought it from a shop near the supermarket
Go take a bath now
Who is it?
What's wrong?
Did you hear it? The sound of something broken
It's dangerous. Go back into the house
Would it be a broken window?
But I don't see anyone
Let's report it to the police
Maybe it's just a prank of some naughty kids
The deal is always successful when Saya is there
I'm losing my confidence
Everyone knows I'm new so they treat me nicely
I have a lot to learn from Mr Kosaka
I'll spare more time for you
Just leave it to me
Manager, here're the quotations of
last week's new system
Thank you
Do you have a minute?
What's the matter?
It's about Mr Kosaka
Kosaka?
He's trying to date me. I don't know what to do
It may not be as serious as you think
He isn't ill-intended
I'm scared
If he knew you're not interested, he'd give up
Sorry for taking up your time
I know a nice shop in Kagurazaka
Fancy try it together?
Really? That's great
- I'm making a reservation then
- Alright
Let's not chat here. We'll be told off
Right. See you
Kadokura, did you go to the alumni gathering?
Yes, it'd be perfect if you were there
Did Saori Amami go too?
You're mentioning a girl! How rare?
It just came across my mind
No, but her daughter came
She really takes after her mom
We're all shocked
Hey?
It hurts
Tota
Amami
The teacher's not here
Are you okay?
- Can you stand?
-Uh
Ly down
I'm sorry, I suffer from anemia
Tota
can you keep me company here? I'm scared
I'm sorry
Tota
Manager
What's the matter?
I can't find Kubo Fabric's
presentation information
I just used it in the meeting
I'll check it out in the conference room
Thank you
Not at all. I'm about to off now
Really?
Manager seldom loses his documents
Sorry to keep you here searching for it with me
Not at all
We're meeting up after work anyway
1f you left alone earlier, I'd be shocked
This place is abnormally quiet at this moment
I wouldn't be surprised if someone sneaked in
and did something fishy
Something fishy?
I meant something fishy
Where is it?
Mr Kosaka, I found it
Oh no...it's revealed?
Sa...Saya
Stop it, Mr Kosaka
No! Stopt it!
Stop it!
Kosakal
What're you doing here?
Get dressed
Amami
How'd this happen?
I've had enough of this
Calm down please
I want to quit
What're you talking about?
I'm really sorry
If only I had listened to you
No. I've calmed down
It's not your fault, manager
I misled him
No, it's not your fault
But I made him think we're dating
I'll talk with Kosaka
They're right. You're really thoughtful
Not at all
Excuse me, I need to phone home. I'll be back
Alright
Manager
What's wrong?
What happened exactly?
What nonsense is it?
I'm drunk
I've sobered up
No way!
Don't you remember?
Anyway, get dressed first
It's my first time
But I don't regret
Are you tired?
You're on the schmooze up til now?
They really liked drinking
You woke up already?
I always wake up at this time
Don't you know?
Really?
You're with a female client?
It'd be Tsuboi's. She's there too
The one I introduced to you last time
How'd you bring a young girl to a pub?
The client likes her
Are you taking a nap?
I have to go after a shower
What have you don't wrong when I'm away?
Say it...what do you introspect for?
Why you had your hair cut?
I've determined to work hard
It looks fresh and nice
Good morning
Don't worry. Manager would forgive anyone
who's capable of his work
Manager
I'm really sorry
Follow me
Kosaka, you'd forget about Amami
I plan to apologize to Saya
No need. Just don't have any connection with her
But...we're seeing each other
It's just a misunderstanding yesterday
Don't be silly
Listen, forget about Amami
I'm sorry about what happened yesterday
I didn't expect that
Doing such a thing in the office
Psycho!
- Amami, go back to the office first
- Yes
Manager
Tsuboi
What has Kosaka done?
It's taken care of now
Please tell me. We're of the same team
It's okay now. Don't worry
Okay. But you don't have to
keep everything from me
I'm confident I'll earn your trust
Thank you
Manager
Manager, fancy have dinner with me?
I need to talk to you about
what happened last night
I'm sorry. I'm not free
I know, it's just between you and me
How about this?
I really don't remember anyone
Got you, great!
What're you doing here?
I said I needed to talk to you
Good. Let's fix a time. You go home first
You live nearby
How do you know?
I know lots more than this
Your wife's name and her email address
How do you know?
You took a rest last night
Makoto
I wonder what your wife would think
after seeing this
How about sending this to her email
- Stop it
- Don't
This is the punishment for avoiding me
You gotta rush home faster my email reaches her
Stop it. Don't
- Send
- Stop it
This is... a revenge
(You've got a mail.)
I'm getting out of here
Let's count 1 to 10.
No..I'mno longer a kid
Count 1 to 10 with mom.
Ready...1..2..3.4
5.6.1.8.9.10
Mom, you've got a mail
Momoko, come and dry your hair
or you'll get a cold
Momoko, go brush your teeth
Yes, mom
Momoko
Daddy, when did you get home?
Just now
I'm sorry, I broke your phone accidentally
Ridiculous! It's careless of you
I didn't know it was on the sofa
Why are you sweating so badly?
Am 17
I was chased by a dog so I ran home
I was scared and I thought I might get bitten
Daddy, what're you doing?
Get up quickly
Someone from the office is here for you
Good morning
That's a nice song
Manager, good morning
Ms Amami comes to delivery
the documents on a holiday
Manager asked me to introspect at home
but I turned in my work late
Makoto, go get changed. It's impolite of you
I'm sorry, he shouldn't have got up so late
Manager must be very tired
Momoko, go back to your room to practise
Momoko, you have some homework to finish
Let's do it now
Take your time and have a good chat
I'm leaving soon
- Momoko, goodbye
- Let's go
What do you want?
Manager, here's your document
To my surprise, she didn't see the email
Go home
Since I've come, show me more of your stuff
That's enough
What do you mean?
I really can't remember anything
I was never drunk
Did we
You meant I lied?
Why would I lie?
Makoto, can you come over here?
What's the matter?
I'm meeting the tutor, I gotta go
Tutor?
Did you forget?
It's the tutor for Momoko
I got it. Go ahead
I'll be back soon
Alright
You might as well invite Ms Amami to
have lunch with us
No need, she's leaving soon
Really? I'm leaving
Alright
See you soon
Take care
The bedroom is upstairs?
Stop messing around
Don't shout or you'll alert Momoko
What do you want exactly?
Get out of here
No decorations. Nice place
Alright. You should leave now
The more your kid grows,
the less sex you with your wife?
Which one is a better partner, me or her?
Nonsense
I resemble my mom's face
Who are you exactly?
You forgot my mom completely?
You dare not admit it
Don't get violent
You want to run for the email again?
Just do what you're told
Agree?
Get dressed
You can call Momoko in
Actually, you feel great
I've fulfilled my mom's wish
It's natural that you forgot
You didn't have any relationship back then
What do you want exactly?
I won't forgive you
Why?
For my mom
There's nothing between your mom and me
Right. You never had any relationship
That's why I can't forgive you
20 years ago,
when you ran away from the medical room
That's unforgivable
Tota
I'm sorry
You ran away anyway
Did Amami tell you so?
So what?
If you had stayed in the medical room,
my mom wouldn't have been
Tota
Stop it
She gave birth to me
The feeling of a mom who doesn't want her baby
could you imagine that?
You knew nothing and carried on your life as usual
1l ruin your life
I...
I'm home
Daddy, are you here?
Daddy, what's wrong?
Where's Ms Amami? She's gone?
She's left
Qutrageous. Though I'm not as useless as Kosaka,
the clients just ignored me when you're around
Ms Sakiko, can I talk with you
before we get back to the office?
Of course. What's the matter?
Manager Tota has been harassing me
What? What's that nonsense!
At first it's about work
But later
What happened later?
Ridiculous...and shameful
Why do you lie about that?
I didn't
I can only tell you, Ms Sakiko
What's wrong with you? Don't do that
Manager
Thanks for your hard work
Harvest's order has been progressing smoothly
Great. How's Amami's performance?
Oh?
I want to know if she's good for the job
She's fine
Got it. Follow up Kubo Fabric's order as well
Yes, sir
What's wrong?
Nothing
Tell me
I've got an email from the intranet from manager
You'd take the picture by yourself
I know manager so well
I've been working with him since
I joined this company
Compared with him, you're not trustworthy
I'm home
Welcome home
Mom, you got anything to eat?
Momoko, the girl from
daddy's office came yesterday?
Did you go into mom's room?
I think so
With daddy?
She didn't feel well and lied down
Really?
Mom, daddy is a liar
What did you say?
He broke your phone deliberately
I saw him telling lies
That's impossible for dad to tell lies to mom
I saw it
But there's no reason for daddy to
break mom's stuff
How'd I know? Go ask him yourself
Momoko
Hey girl, where're you going?
I got it. You're Momoko Tota
Nice to meet you
We'll learn together from today onwards
My name is Shingo Hayakawa. Nice to meet you
I'm sorry, I arrived early
I'm from the tutorial school. I am Hayakawa
I'm the one to apologize. We're not ready yet
The teacher is nice. That's great
Momoko seems to get along with him
Did you hear me?
You're talking about the tutor
Are you tired?
Not really
I'm sorry
I'm really a bit tired
(I've got something important to tell you.)
You may leave too
I've got something to attend to
What? Go home if it's not important
I can't refuse him
(Meet me at the Information Room at 6p.m, Tota.)
Ignore him, go home
What do you want to tell me?
Let's do it here
Stop it
Or you prefer doing it with me in your bedroom?
Why are you doing this?
Anything as long as it's pleasant
I'll shout
You'll be in trouble if we are found here
Don't you understand?
Stop it
I'm eager to quit anytime for a company like this
Hurry up
Faster
You must finish it
- It's finished
- Nice song
How about playing it once again?
I'm home
Saya
You go home first. I have a place to visit
Alright
Saya
Don't give up
Thank you
Who's this?
I'm Manager Tota's subordinate
called Sakiko Tsubol
I have something important to tell you
It may surprise you but please listen to me
Can you write C?
- Cishere
- Write C
Look
English is a world language
What's the matter?
I'll check it out
No, I'll go check it out
Momoko, you have to fill the page with Cs
No problem. Just a piece of cake
Are you alright?
I'm sorry, I was careless
What happened?
I'm sorry. You don't have to tell me
I'll take these away
Excuse me
Take a good rest. You look unwell today
I'm home
Sawako
Don't ever put your feet on the room
Mom
From now on, I'll help you
punish him by ruining his life